Guide to the Charles Alexander Beardsley Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Charles Alexander Beardsley papers
1930-1941
SC0276
Beardsley, Charles Alexander, 1882-1963.
1 Linear feet
This collection consists largely of press clippings and editorials about his law career, 1939-1940, but also includes a bibliography and reprints, 1930-1940, and two certificates, 1940-1941.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Charles A. Beardsley earned his A.B. at Stanford University in 1906 and his J.D. in 1908. He pursued his law career in Oakland, California and was one of the organizers of the State Bar of California, serving as its president in 1929 and 1930. He was also active in the American Bar Association.
Description of the Collection
This collection consists largely of press clippings and editorials about his law career, 1939-1940, but also includes a bibliography and reprints, 1930-1940, and two certificates, 1940-1941.
Access Terms
Beardsley, Charles Alexander, 1882-1963.; Lawyers--California.
Collection Contents
- Papers, 1930-1941
  - Newspaper clippings, 1940 Mar-Jul (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Certificates, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bibliography, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reprints, 1915, 1930, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1940 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1939 Mar-Jul (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings (editorials), 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1939 Dec - 1940 Feb (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1939 Sep (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1939 Oct-Nov (Box 1, Folder 11)